MALLOMBASI MATTAWANG

PHP DEVELOPER

TENTANG SAYA

Saya seorang pengembang aplikasi yang energik dan bersemangat mencari peluang untuk meningkatkan kemampuan saya di organisasi terkemuka. Saya memiliki pengalaman kerja di PHP, Yii2, Codeigniter, Laravel dan Node express dan tertarik mengembangkan aplikasi javascript kedepannya.

SERTIFIKASI

Dasar Pemrograman JavaScript Dicoding Indonesia2021-06-12

https://www.dicoding.com/certificates/ERZR535E2PYV

Aplikasi Back-End untuk Pemula Dicoding Indonesia 2021-06-09

https://www.dicoding.com/certificates/MEPJ51M2WP3V

Fundamental Front-End Web Development Dicoding Indonesia 2021-05-18

https://www.dicoding.com/certificates/MRZMGR03KZYQ

Front-End Web Developer Expert Dicoding Indonesia 2021-06-11

https://www.dicoding.com/certificates/07Z6L1YDJPQR

Cloud Practitioner Essentials (Dasar AWS Cloud)

Dicoding Indonesia 2021-06-19

https://www.dicoding.com/certificates/MEPJ54L2LP3V

CONTACT

mattawang.rpl@gmail.com

+62 813-9847-8284 / Wa: +62 853-9696-6192

• Perumahan Tambora Land III, Blok C/15, Kec.Baro mbong, Kab.Gowa

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/mattawang-91

PENGALAMAN KERJA

PHP Codeigniter developer

Info Tech Solutions May 2018 - Present

- Working on Project estimates
- Implement code based on project specifications.
- Setup and create a new table within MySQL.
- Testing and QA Handover document.
- Giving a feedback to the development group to improve Agile Project management methods.

PHP Program Developer

New-land Solutions Ltd Apr 2017 - May 2018

- Communicate with product and engineering team members to define and develop new software product concepts.
- Improvement of system architecture by refactoring old legacy code to the latest technology.
- Coordinated with the QA testing team for endto-end unit testing and post-production testing.
- Coded user frendly applications that converted raw data from design engine to easily understandable graphical formats.

PHP Developer

Atlantic Soft Technologies 2016 - Mar 2017

- Build a cross-platform activity feed client for the social software product.
- Build mobile applications for multiple platforms.
- Implemented application security and data assurance software.
- Analysis of requirements and used systematic approaches to implement code.

PENDIDIKAN

Masters Of Computer Science University of California, Los Angeles Feb 2012 - Feb 2016

KEAHLIAN

PHP, MySQL	
Mvc Yii2	
Mvc Codeigniter	
Mvc laravel	

JavaScript	
Node JS,Node express	
Git(github, gitlab)	
Bootstrap HTML/CSS	

KEAHLIAN LAIN

Fotografi Adobe Photoshop Adobe Indesign